<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Writings on </title>
    <link>https://breschke.github.io/writing/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Writings on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Copyright (c) 2017, Brian P. Reschke; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 22 Mar 2016 09:50:51 -0600</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://breschke.github.io/writing/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Deference</title>
      <link>https://breschke.github.io/writing/status-deference/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Mar 2016 09:50:51 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://breschke.github.io/writing/status-deference/</guid>
      <description>I met Joel Baum at the Winter Strategy Conference in March 2016. We discussed an extension of the status spillovers paper that would consider the more dynamic nature of status.
Questions Prompted by the Conference, Irrespective of Data Availability When a status shock arrives, what do neighbors subsequently do? How would the expectations of @rescazoustua16 change with a more dynamic setting? What this is getting at is the fact that in science, status is more cumulative than other contexts: barring an egregious transgression (e.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Sociology of Rivalry</title>
      <link>https://breschke.github.io/writing/rivalry/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Dec 2015 00:31:53 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://breschke.github.io/writing/rivalry/</guid>
      <description>Abstract: Initial thoughts on rivalry as a distinct sociological construct. I wrote much of the following in Spring 2011.
Introduction Uzzi (1996) makes the embeddedness hypothesis (Granovetter 1985) actionable; his results suggest that the degree to which a firm concentrates its exchange in few or many partners, and the degree to which a firm’s partners do the same, matter to a focal firm’s survival. Whereas the survival returns to ‘first-order’ embedded ties increase monotonically, the relation between partners’ network characteristics and the focal firm’s survival is curvilinear (U-shaped).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Spillovers</title>
      <link>https://breschke.github.io/writing/status-spillovers/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Dec 2015 12:17:54 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://breschke.github.io/writing/status-spillovers/</guid>
      <description>When an actor experiences a sudden gain in status — for example, when a scientist wins a Nobel Prize, or a film director wins an Oscar — what does this jump in status do to the fates of the winner’s many ‘neighbors’? Do non-winners bask in the reflected glory of the winner, and therefore rise with her? Or conversely, does competition for attention ensue, attenuating the recognition neighbors otherwise would have received?</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>