<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title></title>
    <link>https://breschke.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Copyright (c) 2017, Brian P. Reschke; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 03 Sep 2019 05:04:07 -0600</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://breschke.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Lifelong Learning, Service, and Faith, Hope, and Charity</title>
      <link>https://breschke.github.io/idea/idea2019092460449/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Sep 2019 05:04:07 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://breschke.github.io/idea/idea2019092460449/</guid>
      <description>Origin Story Sister Christine Herlevi taught us in Sunday School two days ago. We discussed faith, hope, and charity, and their interrelation.
Summary The aims of a BYU education include a commitment to lifelong learning and service. How is learning dependent on ongoing service?
Next Steps What if we held a simple innovation skill assignment in November to provide pro-bono consulting to a friend or family member using principles of the course?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sharing Time or Reinforcement Prelude</title>
      <link>https://breschke.github.io/idea/idea2019092460507/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Sep 2019 05:04:07 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://breschke.github.io/idea/idea2019092460507/</guid>
      <description>Origin Story Summary Next Steps What if we started every class by reinforcing a previous principle through a simple application?
&amp;lt;#refend&amp;gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Verb of the Week - Teach One Another</title>
      <link>https://breschke.github.io/idea/idea2019092460509/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Sep 2019 05:04:07 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://breschke.github.io/idea/idea2019092460509/</guid>
      <description>Summary Earlier, I had the thought of structuring class around &amp;lsquo;verbs of the week&amp;rsquo;. It&amp;rsquo;s true that we&amp;rsquo;re focusing on a general theme each week; the question is what verb to use for each one.
Next Steps Try this out next week  &amp;lt;#refend&amp;gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fri, Aug 30, 2019 3:21</title>
      <link>https://breschke.github.io/idea/abstractionexercise/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2019 03:21:57 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://breschke.github.io/idea/abstractionexercise/</guid>
      <description>Origin Story During dinner last night, I gave the family the following scenario:
 &amp;ldquo;A local doughnut shop owner has promised you $25 if you can come up with a successful, new kind of doughnut. What do you propose?&amp;rdquo;
 Maddie said a banana split doughnut. Cami said a German pancake doughnut, and a snickerdoodle doughnut.
I realized that we could generate many more doughnut ideas if we abstracted each idea to a concept, then generated more ideas out of that concept.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://breschke.github.io/idea/mudslide/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Oct 2018 20:38:21 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://breschke.github.io/idea/mudslide/</guid>
      <description>Origin Story The Pole Creek Fire conversation has shifted from containment to mudslide concerns. I wondered: do we have &amp;lsquo;mudslide fighters&amp;rsquo;? Is this a common concern after fires? If an objective of firefighting is to protect residences, are federal relief efforts as focused on mudslide prevention as they are on burned structure prevention? Whose &amp;lsquo;job&amp;rsquo; would it be to help deter mudslides
Summary Conceptual prototype: when fighting incline fires that threaten homes, dig firebreaks in a way that simultaneously deter mudslides.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ponder Preface</title>
      <link>https://breschke.github.io/idea/ponder-preface/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2017 20:38:21 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://breschke.github.io/idea/ponder-preface/</guid>
      <description>Origin Story Attending the self-reliance training on Sunday, I participated in a condensed version of a self-reliance group meeting that was guided by the Foundations curriculum. The lesson we reviewed used a brief ponder activity at the beginning: reading a scripture from John and reflecting on its meaning. Doing something like this at the start of TCMs or class would help set the tone for discussion.
Summary Start class, TCMs, presidency meetings, (suggest in) couple counsels with a relevant verse of scripture and a simple application question.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Recent Acceptance? Choose Lunch</title>
      <link>https://breschke.github.io/idea/idea2017092510157/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Sep 2017 13:57:40 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://breschke.github.io/idea/idea2017092510157/</guid>
      <description>Origin Story Going to lunch as a department, we congratulated Chad on his recent acceptance at Org Science. We were having difficulty choosing where to go.
Summary What if we awarded the person with the most recent acceptance the standing right to choose where we eat as a group? They do this till the next acceptance.
Next Steps Suggest this rule next Friday, Sep 15, 2017.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Howell and Madsen (2017) Extension</title>
      <link>https://breschke.github.io/note/note2017092511140/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Sep 2017 11:40:52 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://breschke.github.io/note/note2017092511140/</guid>
      <description>What if Taeya and Peter obtained data from the Missionary Department to study variation in missionary mental health and ‘socialization processes’?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Howell and Madsen (2017) Extension</title>
      <link>https://breschke.github.io/idea/idea2017092511141/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Sep 2017 01:13:48 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://breschke.github.io/idea/idea2017092511141/</guid>
      <description>Origin Story Met in writer&amp;rsquo;s circle Fri, Sep 8, 2017 and reviewed introduction to Taeya and Peter&amp;rsquo;s new project on newcomers and the onset of depression / suicide.
Summary What if Taeya and Peter obtained data from the Missionary Department to study variation in missionary mental health and &amp;lsquo;socialization processes&amp;rsquo;?
Next Steps Ask Julia Carlson if she has a connection to the missionary department.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Start Class with a Mini-case on a Current Event</title>
      <link>https://breschke.github.io/idea/dailydigit/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Sep 2017 01:49:12 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://breschke.github.io/idea/dailydigit/</guid>
      <description>Origin Story Listening to a news podcast on the way home yesterday, I recognized an opportunity to talk about Walmart&amp;rsquo;s new &amp;ldquo;free&amp;rdquo; grocery pickup service and Lego&amp;rsquo;s recent challenges. Imagine how refreshing it would be to bring in recent news items and throw it out to the class.
Summary As I am reading/listening to current events during the week, identify connections to course concepts. Use these to jumpstart a discussion in class.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Innovation and Entrepreneurship Course Slides</title>
      <link>https://breschke.github.io/presentation/course/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Sep 2017 12:43:08 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://breschke.github.io/presentation/course/</guid>
      <description>Course Introduction
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mini Sabbaticals</title>
      <link>https://breschke.github.io/idea/idea2017092491110/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Sep 2017 11:10:30 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://breschke.github.io/idea/idea2017092491110/</guid>
      <description>Origin Story I received an email from a colleague currently on sabbatical. I thought about how interesting it must be to go to a different place and try out new lines of research. This prompted the question, &amp;ldquo;Why are sabbaticals so infrequent?&amp;rdquo;
Summary Using the Strategic Inventive Thinking principle of division, I would split sabbaticals up and make them smaller but more frequent. Imagine the recombinatory power of faculty getting out and trying something new on a regular basis.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Faculty Development Plan</title>
      <link>https://breschke.github.io/plan/faculty-development-revised/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Aug 2017 01:20:12 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://breschke.github.io/plan/faculty-development-revised/</guid>
      <description>Abstract: The following plan was developed as part of the Faculty Development Series at Brigham Young University. The intent of this plan is to aid my development in scholarship, teaching, and citizenship over the coming academic year, and to set a foundation for my continued contribution to the mission and aims of BYU. For each professional area—scholarship, teaching, and citizenship—I provide (a) a self-assessment of my performance and abilities, and (b) goals and plans for the year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Review: Evans and Jovanovic (1989) An estimated model of entrepreneurial choice under liquidity constraints</title>
      <link>https://breschke.github.io/note/evanjova89/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 May 2017 09:25:33 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://breschke.github.io/note/evanjova89/</guid>
      <description>RQ “Do liquidity constraints hinder people from starting businesses?” (Evans and Jovanovic 1989, 808).
Situation Knight (1921) argues bearing risk is fundamental to entrepreneurship, while Schumpeter (1934) argues entrepreneurs identify arbitrage opportunities while capitalists bear the risk.1
Questions  Difference between moral hazard and adverse selection? What is the current role of the U.S. Small Business Administration? How would it be affected by the current (Thu, May 4, 2017 9:28) administration’s proposed budget?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Experiment to Assess Status Dilution</title>
      <link>https://breschke.github.io/idea/idea2017041150254/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Apr 2017 14:55:03 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://breschke.github.io/idea/idea2017041150254/</guid>
      <description>As more and more prizes given, how accelerate the depreciation of focal status?
&amp;lt;#refend&amp;gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>McCray and Lee, 2013: MeSH Taxonomy</title>
      <link>https://breschke.github.io/note/mccrlee13/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Jan 2017 12:04:02 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://breschke.github.io/note/mccrlee13/</guid>
      <description>Prep for conversation with Toby and Pierre.
How often do entry terms that were previously distinct become synonyms? Preferred descriptor has multiple entry terms.
Descriptors that appear in multiple locations in the hierarchy. Are these granted more exposure?
Loss of eponyms?
Persistence of use of eponym?

References</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Collins (2000)</title>
      <link>https://breschke.github.io/note/coll00/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jan 2017 11:30:34 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://breschke.github.io/note/coll00/</guid>
      <description>Summary of “Situational Stratification: A Micro-Macro Theory of Inequality” by Randall Collins Retrieved through reading @bothhayn10:
 “Collins’s (2000, pp. 29–33) conception of deference as inherently local and situational points to another predetermined limitation on the Matthew Effect. According to his theory, status accrual is particularly likely to occur in networks of individuals centered on a common base of specialized knowledge. Chances for growth in status are thus constrained by others’ inability to properly appreciate a (local) maven’s worth, and so high-status individuals are often confined to a finite base of focused admirers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Functionalism</title>
      <link>https://breschke.github.io/note/functionalism/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Sep 2016 09:52:23 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://breschke.github.io/note/functionalism/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Fri, Sep 23, 2016 9:55 - I recently accessed Kieran Healy’s syllabus for his contemporary sociological theory course (see here) and have started an individual study course. The first session is on ‘functionalism and its discontents.’ This seems to be a bridge from courses in ‘classic’ sociological theory:
 Last semester, you followed the more or less conventional sequence of “classical” socio- logical theorists through the long nineteenth century. You ended a generation later with Talcott Parsons’s effort to unify these thinkers into some sort of research program.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What if &#39;bathtime&#39; was like a carwash?</title>
      <link>https://breschke.github.io/idea/bathtimecarwash/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Sep 2016 08:51:58 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://breschke.github.io/idea/bathtimecarwash/</guid>
      <description>Last night with the kids, I realized we weren&amp;rsquo;t going to have enough time to play in the backyard AND have bath time. I thought about the speed of a carwash and how the kids find this enjoyable even though it is short. &amp;ldquo;What if bathtime was like a carwash?&amp;rdquo;
The result was streamlined baths: they lined up outside the closed shower curtain, soaped up, entered the shower, scrubbed, shampooed, and got out for the &amp;lsquo;towel cycle&amp;rsquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Recombination Curriculum</title>
      <link>https://breschke.github.io/idea/recombcurr/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Sep 2016 17:05:32 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://breschke.github.io/idea/recombcurr/</guid>
      <description>Consider a &amp;lsquo;recombination curriculum&amp;rsquo; in which classes are periodically held jointly for coordination and cross-fertilization.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gould (2002) Status Hierarchy Dichotomy Applied to Categories</title>
      <link>https://breschke.github.io/idea/idea2016092461257/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Sep 2016 12:57:26 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://breschke.github.io/idea/idea2016092461257/</guid>
      <description>Origin Story Reading Gould (2002), I realized that his strategy of nuancing a dichotomy between status hierarchies as &amp;lsquo;emerging from objective differences&amp;rsquo; and &amp;lsquo;enacted by intentional actors&amp;rsquo; could be analogously applied to categories
Summary Some describe categorical boundaries as representing objective differences between candidates. Others view categories as contested, enacted. A third perspective is possible, in which reliance on heuristics on a case-by-case basis (re)produces categorical boundaries.
Next Directions Examine what Rao and Lounsbury write.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Collaborative Ethereum Project on the Social Nature of Money</title>
      <link>https://breschke.github.io/idea/idea2016092450859/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Sep 2016 09:02:10 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://breschke.github.io/idea/idea2016092450859/</guid>
      <description>Listening to a16z podcast on my way to campus, I learned about Ethereum, the &amp;lsquo;next generation&amp;rsquo; of blockchain-based currency. It would be mutually profitable for finance faculty and myself to write a paper on the blockchain currency phenomenon: bring in Zelizer, Zerubavel, Carruthers?
&amp;lt;#refend&amp;gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Spillovers</title>
      <link>https://breschke.github.io/paper/status-spillovers/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Aug 2016 17:56:29 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://breschke.github.io/paper/status-spillovers/</guid>
      <description>When an actor experiences a sudden gain in status — for example, when a scientist wins a Nobel Prize, or a film director wins an Oscar — what does this jump in status do to the fates of the winner’s many ‘neighbors’? Do non-winners bask in the reflected glory of the winner, and therefore rise with her? Or conversely, does competition for attention ensue, attenuating the recognition neighbors otherwise would have received?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mobile Hugo Addition</title>
      <link>https://breschke.github.io/idea/mobilehugo.md/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Aug 2016 22:14:52 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://breschke.github.io/idea/mobilehugo.md/</guid>
      <description>Origin Story Origin: In preparing for 470, I revisited how I keep my idea log. A drawback to the static website format is it&amp;rsquo;s hard to update in the moment when I&amp;rsquo;m away from my computer. I&amp;rsquo;d like to be able to tap out the gist of an idea and have it populate to my website.
Summary Next Directions &amp;lt;#refend&amp;gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Entrepreneurial Analytics</title>
      <link>https://breschke.github.io/idea/entanalytics/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Aug 2016 04:52:21 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://breschke.github.io/idea/entanalytics/</guid>
      <description>Origin Story During the group meeting, Nile observed that 487 is closer to an analytics class than &amp;lsquo;managerial economics&amp;rsquo;. I suggested the name change to &amp;lsquo;Entrepreneurial Analytics&amp;rsquo;. I think we could go further with this and bolster the competency of our students.
Summary  Create opportunities for our students to consult local startups Hold &amp;lsquo;master classes&amp;rsquo; during the course of 470 where I can teach some fundamental analytics tools  R Python Literate programming Jupyter notebook Markdown   Next Directions &amp;lt;#refend&amp;gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Faculty Development Plan</title>
      <link>https://breschke.github.io/plan/faculty-development/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Aug 2016 02:36:23 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://breschke.github.io/plan/faculty-development/</guid>
      <description>Abstract: The following plan was developed as part of the Faculty Development Series at Brigham Young University. The intent of this plan is to aid my development in scholarship, teaching, and citizenship over the coming academic year, and to set a foundation for my continued contribution to the mission and aims of BYU. For each professional area—scholarship, teaching, and citizenship—I provide (a) a self-assessment of my performance and abilities, and (b) goals and plans for the year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Especially for Young Entrepreneurs (EFYE)</title>
      <link>https://breschke.github.io/idea/entcamp/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Aug 2016 11:03:13 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://breschke.github.io/idea/entcamp/</guid>
      <description>Origin Story Driving to campus for the opening session of the University Conference, I was listening to RadioLab&amp;rsquo;s description of medical facility conditions during Hurricane Katrina. I thought about how I need to spend time too thinking about the welfare of my students and role at the university, and I was reminded of the YEAH program at UC Berkeley.
Summary YEAH (Young Entrepreneurs at Haas) enables middle-schoolers from around the country (and world) to have an immersive, experiential experience in entrepreneurship at Haas.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Course Development Project: Final Report</title>
      <link>https://breschke.github.io/plan/fds-teaching-report/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Aug 2016 01:21:19 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://breschke.github.io/plan/fds-teaching-report/</guid>
      <description>Abstract: The following report describes my course development for BUS M 470: Entrepreneurial Innovation.

Course Background I teach Business Management 470: Entrepreneurial Innovation. This is among the first set of courses undergraduate entrepreneurship majors take after being accepted into the major. Additionally, students from other Marriott School of Management majors (strategy, organizational behavior and human resources) take this course as an elective. The purpose of the course is to help students engage in entrepreneurship in an intentional, systematic way, and to gain confidence in their ability to identify and innovate solutions for problems.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Scholarship Strategies Project: Final Report</title>
      <link>https://breschke.github.io/plan/fds-scholarship-report/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Aug 2016 01:20:44 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://breschke.github.io/plan/fds-scholarship-report/</guid>
      <description>Abstract: The following report evaluates my progress towards goals for scholarly development through February 2017.

Goal Progress In the course of the Faculty Development Series, I set three goals for my scholarly development through the beginning of the Winter 2017 semester. As I review my progress towards each goal below, I identify ways that applied the scholarly strategies identified in my Faculty Development Plan. I also identify new insights gleaned from the experience of reviewing my progress, and I articulate plans for future productivity.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Citizenship Project: Final Report</title>
      <link>https://breschke.github.io/plan/fds-citizenship-report/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Aug 2016 01:20:27 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://breschke.github.io/plan/fds-citizenship-report/</guid>
      <description>Abstract: The following report describes my development in citizenship over the course of the Faculty Development Seminar.

Goal Progress As part of the Faculty Development Seminar, I set goals for development as a citizen. Below, I enumerate these goals, report on my progress, and describe lessons learned and future plans for improvement.
Goal: Provide service to the Rollins Center for Entrepreneurship and Technology (CET) by serving as a judge or mentor in at least two campus-hosted competitions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Starlight: June 6-20, 2016</title>
      <link>https://breschke.github.io/plan/starlight-2016-06-06/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2016 10:05:58 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://breschke.github.io/plan/starlight-2016-06-06/</guid>
      <description>We are on the hook to submit an abstract to NEC this Friday. I have a call with Joel on Thursday. Tasks take roughly the following priority:
 Percentile rank for various career variables Assess degree of left-censoring in career histories Narrow sample to star-lit alters only Assess how this addresses extreme values. If necessary, drop top 0.1 percentile. Descriptive statistics for stocks that ever have a star Control observation for each star-lit alter Brokerage stats  Trello</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Starlight: June 6-20, 2016</title>
      <link>https://breschke.github.io/plan/starlight-2016-06-06/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2016 10:05:58 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://breschke.github.io/plan/starlight-2016-06-06/</guid>
      <description>We are on the hook to submit an abstract to NEC this Friday. I have a call with Joel on Thursday. Tasks take roughly the following priority:
 Percentile rank for various career variables Assess degree of left-censoring in career histories Narrow sample to star-lit alters only Assess how this addresses extreme values. If necessary, drop top 0.1 percentile. Descriptive statistics for stocks that ever have a star Control observation for each star-lit alter Brokerage stats  Trello</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>pricing</title>
      <link>https://breschke.github.io/note/pricing/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Apr 2016 21:52:46 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://breschke.github.io/note/pricing/</guid>
      <description>Questions STEP 6: After testing the price, how know you are getting the ‘expected quantities and revenues’?

References</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jensen, Kim, and Kim (2012)</title>
      <link>https://breschke.github.io/note/jensen-kim-kim-2012/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Apr 2016 08:59:16 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://breschke.github.io/note/jensen-kim-kim-2012/</guid>
      <description>Overview Reputation is typically defined as an “overall actor-level assessment” (p. 141) but often results in confounding with status, identity, celebrity. Instead, we define reputation as attribute-specific based on prior behavior and embed in social systems.
Problems with integrative definitions of reputation Vague, poor discrimination from other constructs What seems like a generalized reputation really is based on some attribute anyway (* Still to be explained: why some attribute-specific reputations dominate other attribute-specific reputations—what do audiences anchor on, and why?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Baum, Bowers, and Mohanram (2015)</title>
      <link>https://breschke.github.io/note/baum-bowers-mohanram-2016/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 08:36:08 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://breschke.github.io/note/baum-bowers-mohanram-2016/</guid>
      <description>Summary Interaction among sell-side securities analysts under-researched. Multipoint contact among sell-side securities analysts has not been studied.
Forecast accuracy is a direct point of competition, and information leadership is an indirect point. (Might information leadership be more highly related to star recognition?)
TO DO  Retrieve key readings on mutual forbearance theory (???,(???),(???)) Learn more on information leadership (refs on p. 2)   Questions  Why would more information leadership in own sphere of influence be evidence of mutual forbearance?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>teaching principles</title>
      <link>https://breschke.github.io/plan/teaching-principles/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Apr 2016 07:38:22 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://breschke.github.io/plan/teaching-principles/</guid>
      <description>(2 Nephi 25:4) - “for behold, my soul delighteth in plainness unto my people, that they may learn.” Prepare so that instruction can be plain and not mysterious and convoluted.  2 Nephi. The Book of Mormon: Another Testament of Jesus Christ. https://www.lds.org/scriptures/bofm/2-ne/1?lang=eng.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>garden task rabbit</title>
      <link>https://breschke.github.io/idea/garden-task-rabbit/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Apr 2016 16:56:24 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://breschke.github.io/idea/garden-task-rabbit/</guid>
      <description>Origin Story In a discussion with Ben Beck in office hours Mon, Apr 4, 2016 3:45 PM, we considered the pain of gardening. He is currently focusing on a smart app to inform gardeners when to plant, water, fertilize, etc.
Summary An alternate pain hypothesis is that time required to garden is a deep pain. A rather complex solution would be coordinating the labor market for gardening talent.
Next Directions TO DO: Draft use of this case in the hypothesis building workshop for Seattle.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Simmel on Competition</title>
      <link>https://breschke.github.io/note/simmel-competition/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Apr 2016 14:42:56 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://breschke.github.io/note/simmel-competition/</guid>
      <description>TO DO: Incorporate in statspill  See book here.
Competition is a subset of conflict.
“The foremost sociological characteristic of competition is the fact that conflict in it is indirect.”
“parallel efforts by both parties concerning the same prize”
S distinguishes between the subjective goal and objective result of competition. The prize competitors seek is in the hands of neither.
S focuses on competition where the only adversary in is the aim.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Simmel on Individuality</title>
      <link>https://breschke.github.io/note/simmel-individuality/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Apr 2016 11:23:17 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://breschke.github.io/note/simmel-individuality/</guid>
      <description>See book here.
How Is Society Possible? Kant on Nature:
 Nature is the representation of nature: the way the mind organizes sense perceptions. The different sense perceptions cannot separately compose nature. They must be combined in the mind.  Comparing nature and society  “In the Kantian view (which we follow here), the unity of nature emerges in the observing subject exclusively; it is produced exclusively by him in the sense materials, and on the basis of sense materials, which are in themselves heterogeneous.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Deference</title>
      <link>https://breschke.github.io/writing/status-deference/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Mar 2016 09:50:51 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://breschke.github.io/writing/status-deference/</guid>
      <description>I met Joel Baum at the Winter Strategy Conference in March 2016. We discussed an extension of the status spillovers paper that would consider the more dynamic nature of status.
Questions Prompted by the Conference, Irrespective of Data Availability When a status shock arrives, what do neighbors subsequently do? How would the expectations of @rescazoustua16 change with a more dynamic setting? What this is getting at is the fact that in science, status is more cumulative than other contexts: barring an egregious transgression (e.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Workflow</title>
      <link>https://breschke.github.io/note/1workflow/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Mar 2016 09:37:55 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://breschke.github.io/note/1workflow/</guid>
      <description>Website Wish List  Link to file that opens source .md in Atom  Tue, Mar 22, 2016 9:38
Scripture citations  Multiple references per pair of parentheses Bundle reference section entries by book (e.g, Holy Bible)  - Multiple references per line
Citations (Done) I’m interested in creating HTML pages of my markdown files. There may be a way to use Scratch to get easy in-line citations. Otherwise, I will likely need to create a Makefile that will output markdown files that contain the TOML at the top and the HTML on the bottom.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Federalist No. 2</title>
      <link>https://breschke.github.io/note/federalist-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Mar 2016 12:19:37 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://breschke.github.io/note/federalist-2/</guid>
      <description>Summary The first matter for Hamilton, Jay, and Madison to establish is the need for a united federal government instead of a series of separate state nations or three or four confederacies. This paper appeals to the people’s notion that Providence has given them this land—essentially, ‘God gave it to us as one land, therefore it should remain one land’, or at least, ‘this land has natural features that suggest unity (oceans) over division’.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Federalist No. 2</title>
      <link>https://breschke.github.io/note/federalist-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Mar 2016 12:19:37 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://breschke.github.io/note/federalist-2/</guid>
      <description>Summary The first matter for Hamilton, Jay, and Madison to establish is the need for a united federal government instead of a series of separate state nations or three or four confederacies. This paper appeals to the people&#39;s notion that Providence has given them this land---essentially, &#39;God gave it to us as one land, therefore it should remain one land&#39;, or at least, &#39;this land has natural features that suggest unity (oceans) over division&#39;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>gluten market</title>
      <link>https://breschke.github.io/idea/gluten-free-market/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Feb 2016 13:37:25 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://breschke.github.io/idea/gluten-free-market/</guid>
      <description> Origin Story Prepping for Sunday dinner, I discovered that gluten-free lasagne noodles aren&amp;rsquo;t available locally. Amazon had an erroneous listing for De C.
Customer validation Sat, Feb 20, 2016.
Summary Next Directions </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>uber for drones</title>
      <link>https://breschke.github.io/idea/uber-for-drones/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Feb 2016 13:01:33 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://breschke.github.io/idea/uber-for-drones/</guid>
      <description> Origin Story Summary Next Directions </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>car sharing garage</title>
      <link>https://breschke.github.io/idea/car-sharing-garage/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Feb 2016 13:01:25 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://breschke.github.io/idea/car-sharing-garage/</guid>
      <description> Origin Story Summary Next Directions </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>car sharing airport</title>
      <link>https://breschke.github.io/idea/car-sharing-airport/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Feb 2016 13:01:12 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://breschke.github.io/idea/car-sharing-airport/</guid>
      <description> Origin Story Summary Next Directions </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>hospitals like playgrounds</title>
      <link>https://breschke.github.io/idea/hospitals-like-playgrounds/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Feb 2016 13:00:48 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://breschke.github.io/idea/hospitals-like-playgrounds/</guid>
      <description> Origin Story Summary Next Directions </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>cyber byu education week</title>
      <link>https://breschke.github.io/idea/cyber-byu-education-week/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Feb 2016 13:00:34 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://breschke.github.io/idea/cyber-byu-education-week/</guid>
      <description> Origin Story Summary Next Directions </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>byu affiliate entrepreneurship centers</title>
      <link>https://breschke.github.io/idea/byu-affiliate-entrepreneurship-centers/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Feb 2016 13:00:16 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://breschke.github.io/idea/byu-affiliate-entrepreneurship-centers/</guid>
      <description> Origin Story Summary Next Directions </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>seat belts on buses</title>
      <link>https://breschke.github.io/idea/seat-belts-on-buses/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Feb 2016 12:59:53 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://breschke.github.io/idea/seat-belts-on-buses/</guid>
      <description> Origin Story Summary Next Directions </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>vr graffiti</title>
      <link>https://breschke.github.io/idea/vr-graffiti/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Feb 2016 12:59:40 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://breschke.github.io/idea/vr-graffiti/</guid>
      <description> Origin Story Summary Next Directions </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>classroom probe service</title>
      <link>https://breschke.github.io/idea/classroom-probe-service/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Feb 2016 12:59:24 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://breschke.github.io/idea/classroom-probe-service/</guid>
      <description> Origin Story Summary Next Directions </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>drones construction service</title>
      <link>https://breschke.github.io/idea/drones-construction-service/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Feb 2016 12:59:06 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://breschke.github.io/idea/drones-construction-service/</guid>
      <description> Origin Story Summary Next Directions </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>drone flying lessons</title>
      <link>https://breschke.github.io/idea/drone-flying-lessons/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Feb 2016 12:58:51 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://breschke.github.io/idea/drone-flying-lessons/</guid>
      <description> Origin Story Summary Next Directions </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>sanderson approach</title>
      <link>https://breschke.github.io/idea/sanderson-approach/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Feb 2016 12:58:40 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://breschke.github.io/idea/sanderson-approach/</guid>
      <description> Origin Story Summary Next Directions </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>organizations stifle exit</title>
      <link>https://breschke.github.io/idea/organizations-stifle-exit/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Feb 2016 12:58:16 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://breschke.github.io/idea/organizations-stifle-exit/</guid>
      <description> Origin Story Summary Next Directions </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>prototype ref mgmt software</title>
      <link>https://breschke.github.io/idea/prototype-ref-mgmt-software/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Feb 2016 12:57:56 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://breschke.github.io/idea/prototype-ref-mgmt-software/</guid>
      <description> Origin Story Summary Next Directions </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>councils identify others pain</title>
      <link>https://breschke.github.io/idea/councils-identify-others-pain/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Feb 2016 12:57:33 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://breschke.github.io/idea/councils-identify-others-pain/</guid>
      <description> Origin Story Summary Next Directions </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>busm470 kitchen</title>
      <link>https://breschke.github.io/idea/busm470-kitchen/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Feb 2016 12:56:13 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://breschke.github.io/idea/busm470-kitchen/</guid>
      <description>Reading Tina Seelig&amp;rsquo;s //inGenious//, I liked Matthew Edward Harris&amp;rsquo; description of his experiencing taking the All Soul&amp;rsquo;s &amp;lsquo;one-word&amp;rsquo; entrance exam: &amp;ldquo;like a chef rummaging through the recesses of his refrigerator for unlikely soup ingredients&amp;rdquo; (p. 4). What if the Wilk, or some other kitchen on campus, allowed us to use the facilities to host a &amp;lsquo;chopped challenge&amp;rsquo;? Discuss and debrief?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>core periphery</title>
      <link>https://breschke.github.io/idea/core-periphery/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Feb 2016 09:25:46 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://breschke.github.io/idea/core-periphery/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>creativity study a al tina grey</title>
      <link>https://breschke.github.io/idea/creativity-study-a-al-tina-grey/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Feb 2016 10:18:10 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://breschke.github.io/idea/creativity-study-a-al-tina-grey/</guid>
      <description>What if Tina Grey&amp;rsquo;s process for writing (public, recorded, evaluated?) were applied to generating new ideas. Could we see that sharing ideas (at least the act of articulating them to a public audience) improves (a) volume (b) quality &amp;copy; actionability? I&amp;rsquo;m interested in trying it out with my students and potentially enlisting OB 321 classes in this.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>perceived market share</title>
      <link>https://breschke.github.io/idea/perceived-market-share/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Feb 2016 10:15:24 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://breschke.github.io/idea/perceived-market-share/</guid>
      <description>Context: Chad&amp;rsquo;s class Mon, Feb 8, 2016 11:00 - What if we asked people to estimate perceived market share of a company? Assess: does market share even matter to customers? Is a discrepancy between perceived and actual market share substantive?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>liability of dominant design</title>
      <link>https://breschke.github.io/idea/liability-of-dominant-design/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Feb 2016 10:14:38 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://breschke.github.io/idea/liability-of-dominant-design/</guid>
      <description>While observing Chad&amp;rsquo;s class (Mon, Feb 8, 2016 11:00 AM) in which he led a discussion of Apple&amp;rsquo;s iPod vs. Microsoft&amp;rsquo;s zune, I wondered: when, if ever, is it bad to create the dominant design in an industry? I would like to learn more about this kind of thing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Research Idea: Sounding Liberal</title>
      <link>https://breschke.github.io/idea/talk-liberal-to-me/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Feb 2016 09:54:14 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://breschke.github.io/idea/talk-liberal-to-me/</guid>
      <description>Study the transcripts of presidential debates. Assess the extent to which candidates conform to latent codes of what it is to be conservative or liberal. What about moderates? This could be a natural extension of what I am doing with LLL, and would be something for a more sociological outlet.
Related: Do actions speak louder than words? Symbolic action in votes and language. How well can you finagle your way out of expectations?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>grading pitches</title>
      <link>https://breschke.github.io/plan/grading-pitches/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Dec 2015 17:02:41 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://breschke.github.io/plan/grading-pitches/</guid>
      <description>Considerations  Create a rubric and stick to 5% breaks in scores. Range from 80 to 100, possibly using 80 in exceptional cases only. The distribution should be similar to the final grade distribution.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>grading pitches</title>
      <link>https://breschke.github.io/plan/grading-pitches/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Dec 2015 17:02:41 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://breschke.github.io/plan/grading-pitches/</guid>
      <description>Considerations  Create a rubric and stick to 5% breaks in scores. Range from 80 to 100, possibly using 80 in exceptional cases only. The distribution should be similar to the final grade distribution.  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pricing</title>
      <link>https://breschke.github.io/plan/pricing/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Dec 2015 16:50:22 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://breschke.github.io/plan/pricing/</guid>
      <description> Questions  How is Q* calculated?     </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pricing</title>
      <link>https://breschke.github.io/plan/pricing/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Dec 2015 16:50:22 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://breschke.github.io/plan/pricing/</guid>
      <description> Questions  How is Q* calculated?  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Final Pitch Format</title>
      <link>https://breschke.github.io/plan/final-pitch-format/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Dec 2015 12:54:51 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://breschke.github.io/plan/final-pitch-format/</guid>
      <description> I need them to assume that none of us have seen the pitch before. This will push them to emphasize how the pain exists, is deep, and worth solving.
   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Final Pitch Format</title>
      <link>https://breschke.github.io/plan/final-pitch-format/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Dec 2015 12:54:51 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://breschke.github.io/plan/final-pitch-format/</guid>
      <description>I need them to assume that none of us have seen the pitch before. This will push them to emphasize how the pain exists, is deep, and worth solving.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Use of Prototypes</title>
      <link>https://breschke.github.io/plan/prototypes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Dec 2015 11:14:52 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://breschke.github.io/plan/prototypes/</guid>
      <description> It seems we need to spend more time on how to use prototypes in validation. Getting feedback, good and bad, is crucial to this process. Seeing that we can build it is only part of the prototyping process.
Questions  How can prototypes best elicit customer feedback?     </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Use of Prototypes</title>
      <link>https://breschke.github.io/plan/prototypes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Dec 2015 11:14:52 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://breschke.github.io/plan/prototypes/</guid>
      <description> It seems we need to spend more time on how to use prototypes in validation. Getting feedback, good and bad, is crucial to this process. Seeing that we can build it is only part of the prototyping process.
Questions  How can prototypes best elicit customer feedback?  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Sociology of Rivalry</title>
      <link>https://breschke.github.io/writing/rivalry/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Dec 2015 00:31:53 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://breschke.github.io/writing/rivalry/</guid>
      <description>Abstract: Initial thoughts on rivalry as a distinct sociological construct. I wrote much of the following in Spring 2011.
Introduction Uzzi (1996) makes the embeddedness hypothesis (Granovetter 1985) actionable; his results suggest that the degree to which a firm concentrates its exchange in few or many partners, and the degree to which a firm’s partners do the same, matter to a focal firm’s survival. Whereas the survival returns to ‘first-order’ embedded ties increase monotonically, the relation between partners’ network characteristics and the focal firm’s survival is curvilinear (U-shaped).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bothner, Haynes, Lee, and Smith (2010)</title>
      <link>https://breschke.github.io/note/bothhayn10/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Dec 2015 23:21:01 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://breschke.github.io/note/bothhayn10/</guid>
      <description>Summary When status depends on endorsements, non-stars will eventually attain the status of stars, but when endorsements don’t matter (no spillover effects), then stars monopolize status.
They distinguish between the Matthew Effect at the micro level (Merton 1968, 57–58) and the macro level (Merton 1968, 62). Micro level: high-status actors get more credit than low-status actors. Macro-level: the cumulative advantage enjoyed by high-status actors.
I don’t see much distinction between the two: is it that the micro level considers the individual comparison of one scholar to another, and the macro level is the aggregate effect for the high-status actor?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dental Diagnostic</title>
      <link>https://breschke.github.io/idea/dental-diagnostic/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Dec 2015 21:46:56 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://breschke.github.io/idea/dental-diagnostic/</guid>
      <description>Maddie lost a tooth this evening. As I was brushing my teeth this evening, I wondered whether she has teeth like mine or more like Cami&#39;s. It seems we should be able to learn a lot about our future teeth by sending in recently lost teeth in for lab work. Perhaps DNA/chromosome testing could happen in the same go.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Towards a Sociology of Rivalry</title>
      <link>https://breschke.github.io/post/rivalry-soc/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Dec 2015 22:59:13 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://breschke.github.io/post/rivalry-soc/</guid>
      <description>Towards a Sociology of Rivalry code{white-space: pre;}      2015-12-22T22:59:13-07:00 Towards a Sociology of Rivalry  Abstract: Initial thoughts on rivalry as a distinct sociological construct. I wrote much of the following in Spring 2011.

Introduction Uzzi (1996) makes the embeddedness hypothesis (Granovetter 1985) actionable; his results suggest that the degree to which a firm concentrates its exchange in few or many partners, and the degree to which a firm’s partners do the same, matter to a focal firm’s survival.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prior Distributions</title>
      <link>https://breschke.github.io/note/priors/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Dec 2015 13:14:07 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://breschke.github.io/note/priors/</guid>
      <description>Example:
Let (theta) theta denote the probability of obtaining a head in a coin toss, and assume it is known the coin is either fair (has a head side and a tail side, and each is expected to be observed with similar frequency over many, many trials) or unfair in that it has a head on each side. The possible values of theta
are theta = 1/2
and theta = 1</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Status Spillovers</title>
      <link>https://breschke.github.io/writing/status-spillovers/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Dec 2015 12:17:54 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://breschke.github.io/writing/status-spillovers/</guid>
      <description>When an actor experiences a sudden gain in status — for example, when a scientist wins a Nobel Prize, or a film director wins an Oscar — what does this jump in status do to the fates of the winner’s many ‘neighbors’? Do non-winners bask in the reflected glory of the winner, and therefore rise with her? Or conversely, does competition for attention ensue, attenuating the recognition neighbors otherwise would have received?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>paris</title>
      <link>https://breschke.github.io/project/paris/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Dec 2015 12:04:01 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://breschke.github.io/project/paris/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://breschke.github.io/idea/idea2016102860915/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://breschke.github.io/idea/idea2016102860915/</guid>
      <description>Paper: How to get into a star brokerage
&amp;lt;#refend&amp;gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://breschke.github.io/idea/idea2017041150253/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://breschke.github.io/idea/idea2017041150253/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://breschke.github.io/idea/idea201901311007/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://breschke.github.io/idea/idea201901311007/</guid>
      <description> Origin Story Summary Next Steps </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://breschke.github.io/idea/new2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://breschke.github.io/idea/new2/</guid>
      <description>Hello world</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://breschke.github.io/idea/testing123/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://breschke.github.io/idea/testing123/</guid>
      <description>&amp;lt;#refend&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;#refend&amp;gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://breschke.github.io/presentation/aux/b/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://breschke.github.io/presentation/aux/b/</guid>
      <description>Results Dependent variable:  ratinghigh.rating OLSprobit (1)(2)(3) complaints0.692***0.682*** (0.149)(0.129)  privileges-0.104-0.103 (0.135)(0.129)  learning0.2490.238*0.164*** (0.160)(0.139)(0.053)  raises-0.033 (0.202)  critical0.015-0.001 (0.147)(0.044)  advance-0.062 (0.042)  Constant11.01111.258-7.476** (11.704)(7.318)(3.570)  Observations303030 R20.7150.715 Adjusted R20.6560.682 Log Likelihood-9.087 Akaike Inf. Crit.26.175 Residual Std. Error7.139 (df = 24)6.863 (df = 26) F Statistic12.063*** (df = 5; 24)21.743*** (df = 3; 26) Note:*p**p***p  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://breschke.github.io/presentation/aux/deschhmi/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://breschke.github.io/presentation/aux/deschhmi/</guid>
      <description>Descriptive Statistics for HHMI Investigators  MeanStd. Dev.MedianMin.Max.   Year of Appointment  1992.331  5.181  1993  1984  2003   Year of Higest Degree   1980.662  7.571  1981  1956  1998     Note:*p**p***p  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://breschke.github.io/presentation/deck00/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://breschke.github.io/presentation/deck00/</guid>
      <description>Course Introduction  document.write(&#39;&#39;)    # Innovation and Entrepreneurship ### MBA 670 Marriott School of Business Brian P. Reschke Fall 2017  --- -- *** ## Course Introduction *** speaker notes FTW! could this be any simpler?
## Learning Outcomes 1. Generate creative new ideas 1. Understand customers and competitive contexts 1. Formulate and prioritize hypotheses 1. Design and create elegant solutions 1. Validate entrepreneurial opportunities *** ## Individual Assignments *** *** ## Idea Log ***  “If you want to have good ideas you must have many ideas.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://breschke.github.io/presentation/deck00_470/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://breschke.github.io/presentation/deck00_470/</guid>
      <description>Course Introduction  document.write(&#39;&#39;)    # Entrepreneurial Innovation ### BusM 470 Marriott School of Business Brian P. Reschke Fall 2017  --- -- *** ## Course Introduction *** speaker notes FTW! could this be any simpler?
## Learning Outcomes 1. Generate creative new ideas 1. Understand customers and competitive contexts 1. Formulate and prioritize hypotheses 1. Design and create elegant solutions 1. Validate entrepreneurial opportunities *** ## Individual Assignments *** *** ## Idea Log ***  “If you want to have good ideas you must have many ideas.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://breschke.github.io/presentation/deck01/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://breschke.github.io/presentation/deck01/</guid>
      <description>R&amp;R  document.write(&#39;&#39;)    # R&amp;R ### Innovation and Entrepreneurship ### MBA 670 Marriott School of Business Brian P. Reschke Fall 2017 ## A perspective on entrepreneurship  Entrepreneurship is the relentless pursuit of opportunity without regard to resources currently controlled.  &amp;mdash;Howard Stevenson ## R&amp;R Case * Application of Porter&#39;s Five Forces * Illustration of &#39;Industry Immersion&#39; approach to entrepreneurship  Learning Outcome: Understand customers and competitive contexts ## R&amp;R Case  &#34;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://breschke.github.io/presentation/deck02/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://breschke.github.io/presentation/deck02/</guid>
      <description>Creativity  document.write(&#39;&#39;)    # Creativity ### Innovation and Entrepreneurship ### MBA 670 Marriott School of Business Brian P. Reschke Fall 2017 ## Review: R&amp;R Case * Application of Porter&#39;s Five Forces * Illustration of *&#39;Industry Immersion&#39;* approach to entrepreneurship * Distinctions: * Customer vs. User * Make vs. Buy (Network) * Product vs. Business  Learning Outcome: Understand customers and competitive contexts  ## R&amp;R Case  &#34;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://breschke.github.io/presentation/deck03470/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://breschke.github.io/presentation/deck03470/</guid>
      <description>Status Quo  document.write(&#39;&#39;)    # Understanding and Challenging the Status Quo ### Entrepreneurial Innovation ### Bus M 470 Marriott School of Business Brian P. Reschke Fall 2017 ## Course Progress To-Date 1. Introduction to Three Arenas * Desirability, Feasibility, Viability 1. `Industry Immersion` Approach to Entrepreneurship * Bob Reiss and R&amp;R 1. Introduction to `Domain Search` and Creativity * Piero Presentation * Bolster Creative Confidence 1. `Divergence-Convergence`, Team Formation ## Up-and-Coming 1.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://breschke.github.io/presentation/deck03670/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://breschke.github.io/presentation/deck03670/</guid>
      <description>Status Quo  document.write(&#39;&#39;)    # Understanding and Challenging the Status Quo ### Innovation and Entrepreneurship ### MBA 670 Marriott School of Business Brian P. Reschke Fall 2017 ## Course Progress To-Date 1. Introduction to Three Arenas * Desirability, Feasibility, Viability 1. `Industry Immersion` Approach to Entrepreneurship * Bob Reiss and R&amp;R 1. Introduction to `Domain Search` and Creativity * Piero Presentation * Bolster Creative Confidence 1. `Divergence-Convergence`, Team Formation ## Up-and-Coming 1.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://breschke.github.io/presentation/ent-inv-00/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://breschke.github.io/presentation/ent-inv-00/</guid>
      <description>deck .reveal lo { background: #ffbf46; border-radius: 5px; color: #222; padding: 0px 4px 0px 4px; font-size: 10px; text-transform: uppercase; }   Entrepreneurial Innovation Brian P. Reschke BYU Marriott School of Business Fall 2019  course slides  top Innovation &amp;amp; Entrepreneurship Brian P. Reschke BYU Marriott School of Business Fall 2019   course slides  top Quick Shuffle  course slides  top    00-12: Group 1 50-62: Group 5   13-24: Group 2 63-74: Group 6   25-37: Group 3 75-87: Group 7   38-49: Group 4 88-99: Group 8   Please consider the last two digits of your phone number:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://breschke.github.io/presentation/entinv-final-deck/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://breschke.github.io/presentation/entinv-final-deck/</guid>
      <description>Course Summary  Course Summary  Brian P. Reschke
Marriott School of Business
Fall 2019
Reminders   Student Ratings: Please complete by end of today (Thursday, December 13). Final Idea Logs due today  If submitting a notebook, etc., can give to me now. If submitting electronically, upload to Learning Suite by 11:59 PM tonight. If you have already submitted your log and wish to revise it, please contact Steven.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://breschke.github.io/presentation/lecture6/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://breschke.github.io/presentation/lecture6/</guid>
      <description>8470-Lecture-6-emberjs: Slides  Introduction to Ember and handlebars   Secure Web Application Development  Dr. Hale
University of Nebraska at Omaha
CYBR 8470 - Lecture 6
 become a javascript Today: Ember.JS and Handlebars  Part 1: Client-side App Frameworks
Part 2: Ember.js
 What is Ember.js? Where does it sit in the server stack? Ember bindings (HEAVEN) Handlebars Syntax Integrating 3rd Party jQuery Libraries Using Ember tools Integrating with a server-side API  Part1: Client-side Apps   Why clientside App Frameworks?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://breschke.github.io/presentation/recept-plots1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://breschke.github.io/presentation/recept-plots1/</guid>
      <description> Death by Review  document.write(&#39;&#39;)    # Network Constraint # Betweenness Centrality # Extroversion # Self-Monitoring # Receptivity      function extend() { var target = {}; for (var i = 0; i  Reveal.initialize(options);     $(function(){ $(&#34;#includedContent&#34;).load(&#34;images/table1.html&#34;); });    </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://breschke.github.io/presentation/recept-plots2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://breschke.github.io/presentation/recept-plots2/</guid>
      <description> Death by Review  document.write(&#39;&#39;)    # Network Constraint # Betweenness Centrality # Extroversion # Self-Monitoring # Receptivity      function extend() { var target = {}; for (var i = 0; i  Reveal.initialize(options);     $(function(){ $(&#34;#includedContent&#34;).load(&#34;images/table1.html&#34;); });    </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://breschke.github.io/presentation/starburn-aom-08-04/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://breschke.github.io/presentation/starburn-aom-08-04/</guid>
      <description>AOM 2019 - Guru .reveal .paddingBetweenCols td { padding: 0 15px 0 15px; } .reveal .inverse2 { background: #000000; color: #ffffff; text-shadow: 0 0 20px #333; } .reveal .inverse2 h1, .reveal .inverse2 h2, .reveal .inverse2 h3 { color: #ffffff; line-height: 0.8em; } .reveal .rtable td { border: 1px solid black; padding: 0 15px 0 15px; text-align: center; } .reveal sup { vertical-align: middle; font-size: 0.7em; } .reveal tr:last-child { font-size: .</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>