<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Planning on </title>
    <link>https://breschke.github.io/topics/planning/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Planning on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Copyright (c) 2017, Brian P. Reschke; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 22 Aug 2017 01:20:12 -0600</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://breschke.github.io/topics/planning/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Faculty Development Plan</title>
      <link>https://breschke.github.io/plan/faculty-development-revised/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Aug 2017 01:20:12 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://breschke.github.io/plan/faculty-development-revised/</guid>
      <description>Abstract: The following plan was developed as part of the Faculty Development Series at Brigham Young University. The intent of this plan is to aid my development in scholarship, teaching, and citizenship over the coming academic year, and to set a foundation for my continued contribution to the mission and aims of BYU. For each professional area—scholarship, teaching, and citizenship—I provide (a) a self-assessment of my performance and abilities, and (b) goals and plans for the year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Faculty Development Plan</title>
      <link>https://breschke.github.io/plan/faculty-development/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Aug 2016 02:36:23 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://breschke.github.io/plan/faculty-development/</guid>
      <description>Abstract: The following plan was developed as part of the Faculty Development Series at Brigham Young University. The intent of this plan is to aid my development in scholarship, teaching, and citizenship over the coming academic year, and to set a foundation for my continued contribution to the mission and aims of BYU. For each professional area—scholarship, teaching, and citizenship—I provide (a) a self-assessment of my performance and abilities, and (b) goals and plans for the year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Course Development Project: Final Report</title>
      <link>https://breschke.github.io/plan/fds-teaching-report/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Aug 2016 01:21:19 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://breschke.github.io/plan/fds-teaching-report/</guid>
      <description>Abstract: The following report describes my course development for BUS M 470: Entrepreneurial Innovation.

Course Background I teach Business Management 470: Entrepreneurial Innovation. This is among the first set of courses undergraduate entrepreneurship majors take after being accepted into the major. Additionally, students from other Marriott School of Management majors (strategy, organizational behavior and human resources) take this course as an elective. The purpose of the course is to help students engage in entrepreneurship in an intentional, systematic way, and to gain confidence in their ability to identify and innovate solutions for problems.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Scholarship Strategies Project: Final Report</title>
      <link>https://breschke.github.io/plan/fds-scholarship-report/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Aug 2016 01:20:44 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://breschke.github.io/plan/fds-scholarship-report/</guid>
      <description>Abstract: The following report evaluates my progress towards goals for scholarly development through February 2017.

Goal Progress In the course of the Faculty Development Series, I set three goals for my scholarly development through the beginning of the Winter 2017 semester. As I review my progress towards each goal below, I identify ways that applied the scholarly strategies identified in my Faculty Development Plan. I also identify new insights gleaned from the experience of reviewing my progress, and I articulate plans for future productivity.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Citizenship Project: Final Report</title>
      <link>https://breschke.github.io/plan/fds-citizenship-report/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Aug 2016 01:20:27 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://breschke.github.io/plan/fds-citizenship-report/</guid>
      <description>Abstract: The following report describes my development in citizenship over the course of the Faculty Development Seminar.

Goal Progress As part of the Faculty Development Seminar, I set goals for development as a citizen. Below, I enumerate these goals, report on my progress, and describe lessons learned and future plans for improvement.
Goal: Provide service to the Rollins Center for Entrepreneurship and Technology (CET) by serving as a judge or mentor in at least two campus-hosted competitions.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>